http://www.eftta.com/privacy-policy-and-cookies/

Privacy policyand cookies
By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
YOU ARE HERE:
EFTTA
Privacy policy and cookies
We are committed to respecting the privacy of users entering this site and we recognise the importance of the responsible use of information collected on this site. The purpose of this policy therefore is to explain to you rather than appraise you the nature of the information we record and store about you and the way in which it is used. We reserve the right to alter the policy from time to time at our sole discretion.
Data Protection Act 1998
The Data Protection Act defines the legal responsibilities of data users such as ourselves. The Act governs the collection, storage, use and transfer of personal data, for example, name, address, email, age, etc.
Sharing your Data
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
Further Information
Our site may be linked to other relevant sites and where this is the case, this Privacy Policy will not apply to those other sites once you have entered them. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other sites.
Feedback
On our website we may provide space for your comments and/or provide a short survey for you to complete. This is used only to help us refine the content and relevance of our website. It is not re-used or re-applied for any other purpose.
Aggregate Data
In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information about the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website. We only use such data as aggregate. This collected data helps us to determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site for your use.
IP Address
We may collect and track traffic by IP address. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you use your browser on internet. We log this information, but this information is never linked to any personally identifying information. It is used to audit the number of visitors coming to our website.
Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
Cookies
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Contact
European Fishing Tackle Trade Association,
Unit 1.21 East London Works,
75 Whitechapel Road,
